我叫巴里·艾伦  是现今世上速度最快的人
My name is Barry Allen, and I am the fastest man alive.
我年幼时  看到自己的母亲
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
被令人难以置信的东西杀害
by something impossible.
快跑  巴里
Run, Barry, run!
我父亲因为谋杀母亲进了监狱
My father went to prison for her murder.
但是一场事故让我也变得令人难以置信
Then an accident made me the impossible.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但我秘密地用自己的速度打击犯罪
but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
寻找跟我一样的人
and find others like me.
终有一天  我会找到杀害母亲的凶手  妈妈
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother... Mom!
让我父亲沉冤得雪
And get justice for my father.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on The Flash...
你就是他  逆闪电
You're him. The Reverse-Flash.
我是艾尔伯德·斯旺
I'm Eobard Thawne.
闪电侠的速度是
And the Flash's speed is the key
我回到原本时间的关键
to my returning to my time.
《中心城市民报》
危机降临  闪电侠失踪
我被分去跟梅森·布里奇合作  他是个传奇
I've been teamed up with Mason Bridge, who is a legend.
就是你认为哈里森·威尔斯
You're the guy who thinks Harrison Wells
是个疯狂的天才吗
is some mad genius?
你都了解他什么
What do you know about him?
记者梅森·布里奇失踪
我觉得你对威尔斯博士的想法可能是对的
I think that maybe you were right about Dr. Wells.
-哪些想法  -所有的
- Which part? - All of it.
十五年前
睡吧
Come on.
晚安  我的宝贝
Sweet dreams, my beautiful boy.
-妈妈  -巴里  别过来
- Mom! - Barry, no!
-妈妈  -回去
- Mom! - Get back!
妈妈
Mom!
现在
我们知道的哈里森·威尔斯的所有信息
All right, this is everything
都在这里了
that we know about Harrison Wells,
这些信息其实不是很多
which is actually not a lot.
你不是读过一本讲他的书吗
Didn't you read a whole book about him?
是啊  六百页
Yeah, 600 pages,
里面最重要的一点就是  他很神秘
and the big takeaway is, he's enigmatic.
《威尔斯传》
你母亲是被高速者杀死的
Your mom was killed by a speedster.
威尔斯的加速器让你变成了高速者
Wells' machine turned you into a speedster.
对我这个老警察来说  这未免太巧合了
That's way too many coincidences for this old cop.
你觉得他想让我变成闪电侠吗
Do you think that he wanted me to become The Flash?
自从那晚你被闪电击中以后
Everything he's done
他所做的每一件事
since that night you got struck by lightning--
把你带到尖端科研实验室
bringing you to S.T.A.R. Labs,
给你特殊的衣服  训练你
giving you the suit, training you--
这些都是为了保障你的人身安全
it's all been to keep you safe.
还有让我变得更快
And to make me faster.
威尔斯曾说过他需要我变得更快
Wells once said that he needed more speed from me.
为什么
Why?
我也不知道
I don't know.
但他肯定想从你这里得到什么  巴里
But he wants something from you, Barry.
我们只需要搞清楚他想要什么
We just need to figure out what it is.
那就去找他问个清楚
Well, let's go get him then. Let's get some answers.
虽然我们想这么做  但我们不能去
We can't do that now as much as we might want to.
乔  你从一开始
Joe, you had your suspicions about Wells
就对威尔斯有怀疑
from the very beginning.
你觉得他可能是黄衣人
You thought that he might be the man in yellow.
但是你家里留下的血迹与他不匹配
Except the blood from your house didn't match him.
好吧  也许他不是逆闪电
All right, so maybe he's not the Reverse-Flash,
但你认为他知道那晚发生了什么
but you think that he knows what happened that night.
也许他身上有线索  能帮我父亲洗刷罪名
He may have the key to getting my dad out of prison.
不管威尔斯想从你身上得到什么
Whatever Wells wants from you,
这种念头15年前就有了
it started 15 years ago.
他一直都很耐心
He's been patient.
耐心到可怕
Scary patient.
这事儿你得听我的
You gotta listen to me on this.
我们得和他一样耐心
We have to be just as patient.
是啊
Yeah.
亨利
Henry?
Henry!
亨利
-亨利  -亨利
- Henry! - Henry?
好名字
Nice name.
骗到你们了吧
Tricked ya.
看看是谁回来了
Look who's back.
不给糖就捣乱
My tricks. My treat.
不过我会给你们一点甜头
But I'll give you something good to eat.
今日特选  化为灰烬的城市
Today's special. A city in ashes.
魔术师骄傲地欢迎你们来到
The Trickster proudly welcomes you all
最新的混乱世界
to the new disorder.
他在用第三人称说话  这可不是好迹象
Talking in the third person. That's never a good sign.
你生气是因为他给自己起了名字
You're just mad because he named himself.
事实上  名字不是他起的
Actually, he didn't.
二十年前  中城遭到过
20 years ago, Central City was hit by a series
恐怖分子的一系列袭击
of terrorist attacks.
一个人杀害了起码十个平民  两位警察
One man killed at least ten civilians, two cops.
那个人给自己起名叫魔术师
That guy called himself The Trickster.
詹姆斯·杰西今日秘密受审
这个弹力紧身衣还真是酷炫啊
Whoa. Someone was rocking the unitard.
詹姆斯·杰西
James Jesse?
就像杰西·詹姆斯一样  只不过更变态
Like Jesse James, only more twisted.
著名黑帮
杰西先生现在在哪里
Where is this Mr. Jesse now?
詹姆斯·杰西
他被判了好几个终身监禁  在铁山监狱服刑
He's serving several life sentences at Iron Heights.
他算是中城出现过的
He was just about the most dangerous thing
最危险的人物
Central City had ever seen.
那是直到粒子加速器爆炸前
You mean until the Particle Accelerator blew up.
巴里和我去铁山监狱会会这个詹姆斯·杰西
Barry and I will go see this James Jesse at Iron Heights,
看他能否给出什么信息
see if he can give us something
帮我们抓住他的铁杆粉丝
that can help us catch his groupie.
我来分析录像  看能否找出视频来源
I'll analyze the video and see if I can figure out the source.
乔
Hey, Joe.
巴里还好吗  他似乎有些烦躁
Is Barry doing all right? He seems cranky.
就算是闪电侠
Even The Flash wakes up on the wrong side
也有状态不佳的时候
of the bed some mornings.
他没事的
He's fine.
-妈妈  -诺拉  坚持住
- Mom! - Nora, hold on!
巴里  快跑
Run, Barry, run!
吉迪恩  我这是怎么了
Gideon, what's happening to me?
你最近一次对付闪电侠的时间跳跃
Your latest time jump against The Flash
导致了你能力的大量损耗
caused a massive drain on your powers.
你体内细胞里不再含有超速能力
Your cells contain no trace of The Speed Force.
这不可能
That's impossible.
你超速移动和时间旅行的能力
Your ability to move at super-speed as well as travel in time
都被完全耗尽了
has been completely depleted.
那我怎么回去
How am I supposed to get back?
你回不去了
You can't.
闪电侠
第一季  第十七集
从没来过监狱的这一边
Never seen this part of the prison before.
是  我五年前为詹姆斯·杰西
Yeah, I had to have this cell specially built
专门打造了这个单人牢房
for James Jesse about five years ago.
为什么
Why is that?
有个犯罪心理学家曾每周来探访他
A criminal psychologist set up weekly visits with him.
詹姆斯说服他自杀了
James talked the shrink into committing suicide.
你们会需要这些的
Oh, you're gonna need these.
好的
Okay.
先生们
Gentlemen.
请坐
Please, be seated.
我是乔·韦斯特警探  这位是巴里·艾伦
I'm Detective Joe West. This is Barry Allen.
我们想问你几个问题
Uh, we'd like to ask you a few questions.
我能从你口袋里闻到它们的气息
I can smell them in your pocket.
昨天  上百个这样的降落伞炸弹
Yesterday, hundreds of these parachute bombs
被投放至中城各地
were released throughout Central City.
想法很有趣
Fun idea
但并不是个高效的传送系统
but not an effective delivery system.
有多少人死了
How many died?
所幸没有人
No one, luckily.
在我逍遥法外的巅峰时期
You know, when I was free and at my height,
没有人员伤亡的一天就像是
a day without casualties was like--
就像是小熊队赢得冠军
well, like the Cubs winning the pennant--
从未有过
it just never happened.
在降落伞炸弹里找到的炸药
The explosives they found in all the parachute bombs
和20年前你点燃的炸药
had the same explosive composition as the bombs
成分相同
you set off 20 years ago.
这不可能
That's impossible.
配方我谁也没告诉
I never told anyone that formula.
炸药的标志物完全符合
The signatures are an exact match.
他也把自己叫做魔术师
He called himself The Trickster too,
和你一样
just like you.
他和我一点也不像  警探
He is nothing like me, Detective.
完全不像
Nothing!
你知道他是谁吗
Do you know who he is?
如果我知道  一定会告诉你
If I did, I would tell you,
这样你可以找到他  当他的面
so you could find him, cut off his head,
砍下他的头
and throw it right in his face.
很明显这顶多是出自
No, this is obviously the work
业余者的作品
of a rank amateur at best.
不过是觊觎我王位的一个冒牌货
A mere pretender angling for my throne.
我懂你的意思
I hear you.
所以
So...
帮我们抓住他
help us catch him.
证明世上只有一个魔术师
Prove there's only one Trickster.
想在魔术师面前耍花招是吗  约瑟夫
Trying to trick The Trickster, Joseph
不
No.
这事只有一种可能
There's only one way this could happen.
无论他是谁
Whoever he is,
他一定找到了我的老巢
he must have found my lair.
我只求一件事
I ask only one thing,
等你们找到了这个滑稽献丑的小偷
when you find this schtick stealer,
这个诡计多端的攫取者  可悲的冒牌货
this gimmick grabber, this pathetic wannabe, fake,
记得把枪上的保险栓打开
make sure your safety's off.
中城警局
梅森·布里奇一定是出事了
Something has happened to Mason Bridge.
一个礼拜都没人听到他的音信了
No one has seen or heard from him in a week.
他是个记者  也许他在调查什么事
Well, he's a journalist, Iris. Maybe he's on a story.
那他为什么不接电话不回邮件
Then why hasn't he answered his phone or his emails?
也许他查了不该查的事  要低调处事
Maybe he stumbled on the wrong story and he's laying low.
你不像我这么了解他  艾迪
You don't know him like I do, Eddie.
布里奇调查事件时  什么也挡不住他
When Mason is on a story, nothing is getting in his way.
他从不把危险放在眼里
I mean, he considers threats minor annoyances.
那也许他在饮酒作乐或者认识了美女
Then maybe he's on a bender or he met a girl
类似这样所以失联了一周
worth disappearing for a week over.
听着  他还说了尖端科研实验室
Look, he also said that something weird was going on
有不对劲的地方
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
艾迪  他摊上事了
Eddie, something has happened to him.
不好的事情  我能感觉到
Something bad. I can feel it.
求你了
Please.
听着  辛格队长把所有人
Look, Captain Singh has everyone
都派去查中城公园投弹者了
on the Central City Park bomber
但我一有空就去查布里奇的事
But as soon as I can, I'll look into Bridge.
我保证
I promise.
好的
Okay.
看着像是90年代后就没人再来这儿了
This looks like nobody's been here since the '90s.
道具仓库
是啊  快看这个
Yeah, look at this thing.
你真以为杰西不知道
You really think Jesse doesn't know
这个新来的魔术师是谁
who this new Trickster guy is?
他似乎对这个损害他名声的人
He seemed pretty ticked off that someone
非常恼火
was besmirching his bad name.
乔
Joe.
我们看看他在这里藏了些什么
Let's see what he's got stashed in there.
好
Yeah.
-见鬼  -你没事吧
- Damn. - You good?
那个模仿者把所有东西都拿走了
The copycat-- he took everything.
能给我们几分钟吗
Hey, c-can we have a second?
-可以  -只需...
- Yeah, sure. - Just--
爸爸
Dad. Hey.
巴里
Barry.
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?
乔和我想找一个犯人
Joe and I have some questions for an inmate
询问有关爆炸案的事
about a bombing case.
爸爸  我已经接近真相了
Dad, listen, I'm close.
那个陷害你的人...
The man that put you in here--
我就要抓到他了  比任何时候都更接近真相
I'm getting close, closer than I've ever been.
巴里  我们已经谈过这个问题了
Barry, we have talked about this.
我知道  而我不会再谈了
I know, and I'm done talking.
你不应该为别人犯下的罪而付出代价
You're not gonna pay for another man's crime anymore.
坚持住  好吗
Just hang in there, okay?
乔  他到底在说什么
Joe, what's he talking about?
听他的  亨利  坚持住
Like he said, Henry, just hang in there.
怎么  没带糖来吗
What? No candy, fellas?
你让我们去的那个仓库是个陷阱
That storage space you sent us to was booby-trapped.
为保护自己的私人物品
You can never be too careful
再小心也不为过的
with your private things.
那里什么东西也没有
You were protecting nothing.
你的秘密藏匿处已经空了
Your secret stash was empty.
这话什么意思
What do you mean?
没有枪支  没有任何爆炸物
No firearms, none of your explosives,
什么也没有
nothing.
不管你在那里藏了什么
Whatever you had in there,
被偷了  全部被偷了
it was stolen, all of it.
不  他居然偷了我的遗产
No. He's stealing my legacy.
不管这人是谁  你都必须找到他
Whoever this is, you need to find him.
我不会让这个...
I will not let this-- this--
-魔术师  -那是我的名字  我的
- Trickster? - That is my name! Mine!
那屋里有什么  你在那里藏了些什么
What was in that room? What were you keeping there?
一个炸弹  一个真正的大炸弹
A bomb. A really big bomb.
有多大
How big?
能把整个中城都炸掉
Bye-bye, Central City.
-西斯科  -魔术师刚发了条视频博客
- Cisco. - Yo, this Trickster guy just posted a vlog.
你得看看
You gotta see this.
我马上把链接发给你
I'm sending you the link right now.
好
Okay.
中城的居民们
Denizens of Central City,
或者是那些还活着的人
or those of you who remain,
欢迎来爆炸日
welcome to Boom Day.
我很骄傲地宣布我的第一个小把戏
I'm very proud to report that my first trick
取得了前所未有的成功
was an exploding success.
-给他看  -但我认为你们
- Show him. - But I think you all deserve
应得到更大的奖赏
something much, uh, bigger.
-不不不  -所以我的下一个小把戏...
- No, no, no, no, no. - So for my next trick...
把我的面具摘掉  你这个骗子
Take off my mask, you fraud.
伪装者  赝品
Pretender. Sham.
摘掉我的面具
Take off my mask.
Take off my mask!
这是几小时前上传的
This was posted a few hours ago.
不管这个魔术师是谁  显然他并不怕羞
Whoever this Trickster is, he's certainly not shy.
不是每个罪犯都喜欢隐匿在暗处
Well, not every criminal likes to hide in the dark.
西斯科  你能追踪到视频是从哪上传的吗
Cisco, can you trace where the video was posted from?
我试过  但这个人用的是某种疯狂的
I tried, but this guy is using some crazy
费利西蒂水准的扰频器  我从未见过
Felicity-caliber scrambler like I've never seen.
视频的上传源头有几百个
The origin of the upload's coming from hundreds
不同的地点
of different locations.
在他上传另一个视频前  很难追踪到
Until he uploads another video, it's gonna be tough.
这个疯子有摧毁整个城市的能力
This psychopath has the capability to destroy the city.
我说很难  不是不可能
Hey, I said tough, not impossible.
巴里  我们会抓到他的  一向如此
Barry, we'll catch him. We always do.
艾伦先生
Mr. Allen,
单独聊几句
a word please?
我知道你怎么了
I know what's going on with you.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
是吗
Do you?
我知道去铁山监狱
I know going up to Iron Heights prison
跟杰西先生对话
and conversing with Mr. Jesse has brought
让你想起你的父亲
about feelings of your father.
我怎么会不知道
How could it not?
是啊  不  那是
Yeah, no, it's,
知道杀害我母亲的凶手依然逍遥法外
it's been really tough knowing that my mom's killer
让我非常难受
is still out there.
当然
Of course.
不过我们会找到他的  我们一起
But we'll find him, together.
我向你保证
You have my word.
谢谢你
Thank you.
现在  我们还是在别人受伤害前
For now, how about we focus
专心抓捕这个魔术师  好吗
on finding this Trickster before anybody else gets hurt?
能见一面吗
我得走了
I have to go.
不过谢谢你给我打气
But thanks for the pep talk.
我会一直支持你的
I'm always here for you.
研究实验室和政府无关
Research laboratories unconnected to the government,
和任何商业利益无关
unconnected to any business interests
和任何那些东西都无关
or any of that kind of stuff.
现在我们就在市中心建立起来
And then we build right downtown
城市的心脏  城市的焦点
in the heart of the city, in the epicenter,
我们成为了城市的心脏
and we become the heart of the city.
我们成了国家的心脏
We become the heart of the nation.
改变人们看待科学的方式
We change the way you think about the sciences,
然后
and then--
怎么了
What?
我爸爸肯定会跟我一样
Just that my father would have loved you...
很爱你
as much as I do.
真希望能见过你父亲
Well, I wish I could have met him.
你要怎么命名实验室
And what would you call these laboratories?
我们  苔丝·摩根
Well, we, Tess Morgan,
将把他们命名为技术工程
would call them the Technological Engineering
科学研究所  简称  苔丝研究所
Scientific Studies? Or T.E.S.S., for short.
这真是太贴心了
Well, that is very, very sweet.
但是叫
But how about...
科学与技术
Scientific and Technological
尖端研究实验室怎么样
Advanced Research Laboratories?
或者简称尖端科研实验室
or S.T.A.R. Labs, for short?
因为浩瀚的夜空中
Because in the vast night sky,
你  哈里森·威尔斯
you, Harrison Wells,
是我眼中唯一的星
are the only star I see.
这我必须亲你才行了
That's gonna get you kissed.
你现在不已经是全职记者了吗
I thought you were a full-time reporter now.
为什么还在这儿见面
Why are we meeting here?
我还有这里的钥匙
I still have a key.
而且这里对我们意义特殊  不是吗
And this is kind of our place, right?
有什么事
What's up?
我同事梅森·布里奇不见了
My coworker Mason Bridge is missing.
他不在家  不接电话
He's not at home. He's not answering his phone.
这不像他的作风
I mean, it's not like him.
我很担心他是不是出事了
I am really worried that something bad has happened.
他肯定没事
I'm sure he's fine.
艾迪也这么说  大家都这么说
That's what Eddie says. That's what everyone is saying.
拜托了  你能调查一下吗
Please, will you look into it?
为了我
For me?
为了你
For you.
谢谢
Thanks.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你看上去心事重重
You seem like you have a heavy heart.
有时候我不懂
Sometimes I'm not sure
我为什么见你也需要戴面具
why I wear a mask with you.
也许有一天你可以摘掉的
Well, maybe one day you'll take it off.
注意  魔术师又开始广播了
Heads up. Trickster's broadcasting again.
能借用一下你的电脑吗
Can I borrow your laptop?
当然可以
Um, sure.
随便用吧
Help yourself.
准备开始游戏了
Get ready for the games to begin!
我有  一颗炸弹
I have... a bomb.
很大一颗
It's a big bomb.
它会发出巨响
It'll make a big bang
炸出巨洞
and then a big hole
重重坠落在人群之中
and then a big drop in the pop... ulation.
但是千万别说魔术师
But never say the Trickster
耍赖
is not fair.
炸弹在
The bomb is somewhere
52街和B大道之间的某处
between 52nd Street and Avenue B.
所有小组  所有便衣所有警探
I want all units, every uniform, every detective
马上去那个区域搜查
searching that area right now.
我们得想办法通知闪电侠
Somehow we need to alert The Flash.
我觉得他已经知道了
Something tells me he already knows.
伙计们  我找不到
Guys, I can't find it.
我需要你们的帮助
I need your help.
交通摄像头和闭路监控上没有任何发现
There's nothing on traffic cams or CCTV.
我重置了尖端实验室卫星
I retasked the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
去搜寻那个区域的爆炸物
to scan the area for incendiary devices.
那么大的炸弹肯定会发出
A bomb that large should be giving off
某种温度或化学信号的
some kind of thermal or chemical signature.
那为什么找不到呢
Well, then why can't you find it?
因为这是个把戏
Because it's a trick.
炸弹不在那
The bomb's not there.
不  肯定在  我要继续找
No, it has to be. I'm gonna keep looking.
那正是他想要的效果  你和警察
That is what he wants, for you and the police
一直在那个范围内搜寻
to keep running around in circles.
他们的计划不仅如此  巴里
There is something else going on, Barry.
我可以预感到  相信我
I can feel it. Now, trust me.
我要继续找
I'm gonna keep looking.
巴里
Barry?
他为什么不听你的呢
Why doesn't he just listen to you?
我找到了
I found it.
骗到你啦
铁山监狱
铁山监狱发生了爆炸
There's an explosion at Iron Heights.
一个声东击西的把戏
This was all a diversion.
监狱才是真正的目标
The prison was the real target.
詹姆斯·杰西
James Jesse.
我想他骗到了所有人
I guess he's tricked us all.
乔  市里没有炸弹
Joe, there's no bomb in this city.
这是魔术师的声东击西
It was a diversion so the Trickster
为了帮詹姆斯·杰西越狱
could help James Jesse escape.
我知道
I know.
我们刚拿到铁山监狱的监控录像
We just got surveillance footage from Iron Heights.
杰西跑掉了
Jesse got away.
巴里  他们抓了个人质
Barry, look, they took a hostage.
他抓了谁  警卫  监狱长
Well, who did he take? A guard? The warden?
都不是  是你爸爸
No. Your dad.
你不得不承认
You have to admit,
那真是个了不起的小把戏
that was one hell of a trick.
我真不敢相信我们终于共处一室了
I cannot believe we're finally in the same room.
你是我的英雄
I mean, you're my hero.
你需要一个更好的榜样  孩子
You need a better role model, kid.
你没发现吗  你只是在利用你
Can't you see? He's just using you.
我们干嘛非要带上他
Why did we bring him along?
因为他儿子在中城警局工作
Because his son works for the CCPD.
如果我们陷入困境
Should we find ourselves in a jam,
警察的爸爸会是个绝佳的谈判筹码
a cop's dad makes an excellent bargaining chip.
对
Right.
换做我就不会担心
I wouldn't worry too much about
警察会对你做什么
what the cops might do to you.
是吗
Really?
如果警察找不到你
If the police aren't able to find you,
相信我  闪电侠一定会
trust me, The Flash will.
那你就希望着吧
Here's hoping.
下一步做什么
So what's next?
你的最后一封信里提到  你出来后
In your last letter, you said you had something big
有个大计划
in mind for when you got out.
我用了20年精心策划了一个完美把戏
I've had 20 years to come up with the perfect trick.
它将是我最伟大的作品
It's going to be my masterpiece.
我的蒙娜丽莎
My Mona Lisa.
我的《绝命毒师》第五季
My Breaking Bad season five.
为了让我不继续杀狱警
They gave me cable in prison
他们在监狱给我装了电视
so I'd stop killing the guards.
哦对
Right.
还有一个问题我一直想问你
There's just one thing I've been dying to ask.
你为什么选了我
Why did you choose me?
因为我知道你有能力
Because I knew you had the strength
完成我的事业
to fulfill my legacy.
而且
Besides,
这是你的天分
it was in your blood.
等等
Wait.
为什么说是天分
What do you mean in-- in my blood?
我之所以找到你
The real reason I tracked you down
引导你成为最棒的你  艾克索  是因为
and groomed you to be the best you could possibly be, Axel--
我是你父亲
I am your father.
我们确认了另一个魔术师
We were able to identify the other Trickster.
名叫艾克索·沃克  25岁
His name's Axel Walker, age 25.
他和詹姆斯之间的通信
Apparently him and James have been corresponding
已经有十多年了
through snail mail for over a decade.
我应该去监狱的
I should have been there.
我们会找到你父亲的  好吗
We're gonna find your dad, okay?
绝对会
Definitely.
我想我是应该听你的
I guess I should have listened to you.
抱歉  好累哦
Sorry, I am so tired.
我想一到家我就要换上睡衣
I think I'm just gonna put on my pajamas,
直接上床睡觉了
go straight to bed when we get home.
是吗
Really?
算了
No.
还是不穿睡衣睡吧
Definitely not wearing pajamas.
真的呀
Hello.
不不不  泰丝
No, no, no. Tess.
泰丝  泰丝  不要
Tess. Tess! Oh, no.
不  泰丝  泰丝
Oh, no. Tess. Tess.
感谢上帝  救救我
Oh, thank God. You gotta help me.
求你救救我
Please help me.
她  她
She -- she's--
你在干什么  你要干什么
What are you doing? What are you doing?
救救我  叫救护车  叫人来啊
Help. Call someone! Call anyone!
你看不到她要死了吗
Can't you see she's dying?
她几世纪前就已经死了
This woman has been dead for centuries.
救命啊
Help!
你没事吧
You okay?
你觉得我父亲还活着吗
Do you think my dad is still alive?
是的  他活着  肯定活着
Yes. Yes, he is. Of course.
杰西抓走你父亲只是为了当人质
Jessie only took your pop to use as leverage.
他也许是个疯子  但绝对不傻
He might be crazy, but he's not stupid.
而且楼上的所有人都在找他
And everyone upstairs is looking to find him.
所以我应该
So now I'm supposed to just
把我父亲的命运交给一个
leave my dad's fate in the hands of a man
和我母亲的死有关的人手里吗
who may have had something to do with my mom's murder.
乔  我做不到
Joe, I can't do this.
你可以
Yes, you can.
这完全讲不通啊
It just doesn't make any sense.
如果威尔斯是杀人犯
I mean, if Wells is a murderer,
那为什么又要帮我
then why does he want to help me?
为什么还帮我阻止了那么多犯罪
Why has he helped me stop so many criminals?
还救了罗尼
Or saved Ronnie?
我怎么就没看出来呢
Why didn't I see this?
我和他相处的时间大概有你的十分之一
I spent 1/10 as much time with him as you did,
我就差点被他骗了呀
and he almost had me believing in him.
只是差点
Almost.
不管他做了什么
Look, whatever else he is,
他还是哈里森·威尔斯
he is Harrison Wells.
你爱科学  而他就是科学
You love science. He is science.
就好像你和爱因斯坦成了朋友一样
It's like you made best friends with Einstein.
你是说我心甘情愿受骗
You're saying I wanted to be tricked.
你总是想成为一个
You always want to be the person
看到别人优点的人
who sees the best in people.
我当了25年警察了
I've been a cop for 25 years.
我看到的只有缺点
All I can see is the flaws,
谎言
the lies,
和人们以为我看不到的黑暗想法
the dark thoughts that people think I don't see.
我倒希望能像你这样
I wish I could be you.
你的速度  那是你真正的力量
As fast as you are, that is your real power.
不要因为威尔斯就放弃它
Don't let Wells take that from you.
我不知道
I don't know
他为什么帮我们
why he's helping us.
但重要的是他在帮我们
All that matters is that he is.
我不能失去我父亲  乔
I can't lose my dad, Joe.
巴里
Barry.
巴里  好了
Barry, come on.
没事的  没事的
Come on. Come on.
爱瑞丝·韦斯特  《中城新闻图报》的记者
Iris West, I'm with Central City Picture News.
谢谢
Thanks.
香槟  小姐
Champagne, miss?
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
香槟快没了
We're almost out of champagne.
游戏也快要开始了
Then the fun's about to begin.
再选  贝洛斯
贝洛斯市长  你好
Oh, Mayor Bellows, hi.
-这个派对真棒  -谢谢
- This is a lovely party. - Thank you.
欢迎  欢迎  中城的精英们
Welcome, welcome, Central City's finest.
我们向安东尼·贝洛斯市长敬一杯酒吧
How about a toast to Mayor Anthony Bellows?
他不光会吼下属  还会咆哮[贝洛斯]
He doesn't just yell at his staff, he bellows!
听懂我这个双关了吗
You see what I did there with the wordplay and the...
-好多人啊  -抱歉
- Tough crowd. - Excuse me.
你是谁
Who are you?
人们忘得真快
How quickly they forget.
我是詹姆斯·杰西  大人
James Jesse, your honor,
外号魔术师
aka The Trickster.
我是来从金钱手里解放你们这些精英的
And I'm here to relieve you fine people from all your money.
因为能出现在这个房间里的人
Because we know if you're in this room,
都是有钱人
you've got loads of it.
你凭什么认为这里的人
What makes you think that anyone in this room
会把钱给你
would give you a cent?
因为他们刚刚喝下的香槟
Because that champagne they just slurped down
还有果汁喷趣酒里
like so much fruit punch--
被我加了一些特别的东西
I added a little something special to it.
三甲基汞32
Trimethylmercury 32.
毒药
Poison.
没有解药的话  药效出现大概需要
Without the antidote, you'll begin to feel the effects in about,
一小时
One hour.
我记得你
I remember you.
你提前一个小时就来了
You got to the party about an hour early.
第一杯香槟就给了你
I offered you the very first glass of champagne.
一小时的时间足够你们联系银行
An hour is plenty of time for all of you to call your bankers
让他们把你们的钱全都转到
and transfer everything you have to the account number
杯子下面所写的账号上
on the bottom of your glass.
我和我的年轻朋友拿到钱
Once my young friend and I are rich,
就会给你们解药
you'll get the antidote.
可如果你们有谁敢报警
If any of you decide to call 911 instead,
那就尝尝铅中毒
well, then we switch to lead poisoning.
有进展吗
Anything?
我正在扫描全城所有的交通摄像头
I'm scanning all the traffic cams in the city.
-什么也没发现  -宝贝
- I got nothing. - Hey, baby.
爱瑞丝
Iris?
有多少人感觉到了三甲基汞32
How many of you feel the Trimethyline 32
正在你们体内流动
coursing through your veins.
是他  是杰西
That's him. That's Jesse.
-西斯科  能定位她电话吗  -马上
- Cisco, can you ping her phone? - I'm on it.
三甲基汞32是一种作用相当快的毒药
Trimethylmercury 32 is a relatively fast-acting poison.
有解药吗
Is there a cure?
有  我们现在就可以开始合成
Yes. We can start synthesizing the antidote right now.
西斯科  她在哪
Cisco, where is she?
市政厅
City hall.
市长今晚在那举行募捐集会
The mayor's having a fund-raiser there tonight.
巴里  不要小看了魔术师
Barry, do not underestimate The Trickster.
你好啊
Well, hello.
知道吗
You know,
我坐了二十年牢了
I've been in prison for 20 years.
那你再进宫的时候就知道规矩了
Then you'll know the routine when you get sent back.
亨利·艾伦在哪
Where's Henry Allen?
一个你很快就会去的地方
He's where you'll be soon.
天堂
Heaven!
看过《生死时速》吗
Are you familiar with the movie Speed?
基努·里维斯  桑德拉·布洛克演的
Keanu Reeves, Sandra Bullock?
你就是电影里的巴士  那就是炸弹
See, you're the bus, and that's the bomb.
事实上是枚运动炸弹  如果你的速度
A kinetic bomb, actually, and if you go below
低于每小时600英里  它就会爆炸
600 miles per hour, it'll explode.
如果你想拆掉它  也会爆炸
Same thing happens if you try to remove it.
启动了
It's active.
跑  跑  快跑
Run, run, run, run, run.
西斯科
Cisco!
他没骗你
He wasn't lying.
那东西跟一个速度计相连
That thing's linked to a speedometer,
如果你停下  它就会爆炸
and it will blow if you stop moving.
但我不能跑一辈子
I can't run forever.
肯定有办法可以把它完好地取下来
There's gotta be a way to get it off him without damaging it.
巴里  你附近有墙吗
Barry, do you see any walls nearby?
问这干嘛
Why?
因为你需要撞上去
Because I need you to run into one.
更准确地说  是穿过去
Or more accurately, through one.
-什么  -什么
- What?  - What?
如果你能和空气产生共振
If you vibrate at the natural frequency of air,
你的身体  其实是细胞会处于兴奋状态
your body-- your cells will be in a state of excitement
这样你就应该能
that should allow you to phase
穿过一面墙
right through that wall,
把炸弹留在墙的另一面
leaving the bomb on the other side.
-什么叫应该  -你能做到的
- Should? - You can do this.
我相信你
I believe in you.
-我做不到  -听我说  巴里
- I can't. - Listen to me, Barry.
深呼吸
Breathe.
深呼吸  感受空气
Breathe. Feel the air.
感受吹到你脸上的风
Feel that wind on your face.
感受大地  你的脚将你抬升起来
Feel the ground, your feet lifting you up,
向前推进  还有闪电
pushing you forward, and the lightning--
巴里  感受闪电
Barry, feel the lightning.
感受它的力量
Feel its power.
电流在你的血管里穿梭
Its electricity pumping through your veins,
流过了你身体中的每一处神经
crackling through you, traveling to every nerve in your body,
就像触电一样
like a shock.
你不再是你自己了
You're no longer you now.
你融入了更宏大的存在
You're part of something greater.
融入了速度力量
You're part of a speed-force.
它是你的
It's yours.
现在去做吧
Now do it.
巴里
Barry?
感觉好奇怪
Oh, that felt weird.
我没事
I'm good.
账户查看
-我太喜欢这个了  -瞧瞧
- I like it. - Look at that.
龙虾算我账上  孩子
Lobsters on me, kid.
没事的  你们都被注射了解毒剂
It's okay. You've all been given an antidote.
这太不卫生了
That wasn't very sanitary.
亨利·艾伦在哪
Now where is Henry Allen?
反正你也要进监狱了  詹姆斯
You're going to prison either way, James.
行啊
All right.
你就是适合穿红衣服
You always did look good in red.
我实习时  这里一半的东西都还不存在
Half of this stuff didn't even exist when I was practicing.
没错  等你出来后  我很乐意
Yeah, well, I'd be happy to give you
给你上一堂速成课
a crash course on all of it if you get out.
我立刻闭嘴
I'm gonna shut up now.
没事的
It's okay.
-艾伦博士  -嗯
- Dr. Allen? - Yes?
我想抱抱你
I'm feeling the need to give you a hug.
当然  我才不会拒绝拥抱呢
Absolutely. I will always accept a hug.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你得告诉我
Wow. You gotta tell me.
当你像蝙蝠一样穿街跑巷时
What does it feel like when you're running down the street
是什么感觉
like a bat out of hell?
一种独一无二的感觉
There's no feeling like it.
我想也是
I bet.
在我眼里  你们都是英雄
Actually, you're all heroes in my book,
特别是你  威尔斯博士
especially you, Dr. Wells.
谢谢你
Thank you
为我儿子所做的一切
for everything that you've done for my son.
你儿子是个非同寻常的人  艾伦博士
Well, your son is an extraordinary man, Dr. Allen,
我会尽我一切所能来确保巴里的未来
and I will do everything in my power to ensure Barry's future.
该走了  乔
It's time, Joe.
-不用  -不戴手铐
- No. - No?
-不戴  -好吧
- No. - Okay.
觉得你也需要个拥抱
You seem like you could use a hug too.
你父亲是个非同寻常的人
Your father is an extraordinary man.
有他  你很幸运
You're lucky to have him.
有你  我也很幸运
I'm lucky to have you too.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫艾尔伯德·斯旺
My name is Eobard Thawne,
但是名字不重要
but that name doesn't matter.
不再重要了  以后数年也不会
Not anymore. It won't matter for many years.
你是谁才是唯一重要的事
The only thing that really matters is who you are.
哈里森·威尔斯
Harrison Wells.
你在说什么  我不明白
What are you talking about? I don't understand.
在2020年  你和你妻子泰丝·摩根
In the year 2020, you and your wife, Tess Morgan,
成功发射了粒子加速器
successfully launched a Particle Accelerator
改变了历史的进程
that changed the course of history.
我要想回去  要需要它早点发射
I need it to happen a bit sooner if I'm going to get back.
其实需要早很多
Much sooner.
-那是什么  -我回家的路
- What is that? - My way home.
他们不是来救你的
You see, they're not coming to save you.
他们是来救我的
They're coming to save me.
乔
Hey, Joe.
接待警员说你找我
Desk Sergeant said you were looking for me.
艾迪  是的
Eddie, yeah. Uh...
请坐
Sit down.
这件事和爱瑞丝有关
It's about Iris.
她在调查梅森·布里奇的失踪案
She's looking into Mason Bridge's disappearance.
我们不能让她去查
We can't let that happen.
警探
Detective.
艾迪  我们需要你帮忙
Eddie, we need your help.
闪电侠击败魔术师
巴西
Brazil?
为什么  梅森为什么会搬去巴西
Why-- why would Mason move to Brazil?
是为了个女孩
Apparently there was a girl involved,
他决定和她去亚马逊远足一年
and he decided to go hike the Amazon with her for a year,
远离尘嚣
you know, live off the grid,
写写回忆录什么的
write his memoirs or something.
看来人心真是难以捉摸
Wow. I guess you really don't know anyone.
是啊
No, you don't.
宝贝  一切还好吧
Hey, baby, everything good?
还好  当然
Yeah, yeah. Of course.
晚餐马上就好了
Dinner will be ready in a jiff, okay?
好
Okay.
她信了吗
She buy it?
我想是吧
I think so.
为了她的安全  别告诉她真相
Keeping her in the dark, it's for her safety.
这有待商榷  你躲不过去的
That is debatable, and we will have that debate.
但是现在  我们下一步要怎么做
But for right now, what's our next move?
我们要怎样才知道威尔斯的计划
How do we figure out what Wells is up to?
当威尔斯给我讲述如何穿越墙体
When Wells was talking me through phasing
帮我从手腕上摘下魔术师的炸弹
so I could get the Trickster's bomb off my wrist,
他描述成为闪电侠的方式  飞驰感
the way that he described my being The Flash, running,
感受风感受力量
feeling the wind and the power,
就像他在描述他的亲身体会
it's like he was talking from experience.
你想说什么
What are you saying?
我不知道怎么回事
I don't know how...
但是他绝对就是黄衣人
but he's the man in yellow.
哈里森·威尔斯就是逆闪
Harrison Wells is the Reverse-Flash.
发生了一起车祸  可能有人死亡
I got an 11-80, possible 10-54,
J号县公路  请求立即支援
County Road J, requesting immediate assistance.
收到  分队正赶往你所在的位置
Copy that. Units en route to your location.
先生  我们会把你救出去的
Sir, we're gonna get you out of here.
能告诉我你的名字吗
Can you tell me your name?
你知道你是谁吗
Do you know who you are?
我
My name...
叫
is...
哈里森·威尔斯
Harrison Wells.